

zhikiatgan@hotmail.com

Tangkak, Malaysia

+6012-9338220

Profile

Diligent software engineer with 3+ years of experience in banking application and software development. Currently employed with Hong Leong Bank Malaysia, started as a graduate trainee and was promoted to senior executive during my journey. In previous roles, being a team player and ensured 95% on-time project completion. Also, identified issues and dealt with business users to ensure all requirements were met.

Employment History

Sofware Engineer, Hong Leong Bank Malaysia

January 2021 — Present

- Deal with business users/vendor on the scope of work, understand the project and discussion on the feasibility and eliminate most of the issue before development.
- Develop the new functionality/webpage/module to meet the project requirements.
- · Develop REST/SOAP API for mobile applications.
- Join daily/weekly meeting to update the progress or address any issue encounter to the team.
- · Provide support on SIT/UAT and production release.
- On-demand support on the project after release.
- Frontend using Jsf/Primefaces/HTML&CSS
- · Backend using Java/Spring
- Some interesting projects: Project CrossSell QuickCash/FD, Project E-Acceptance (Auto Loan) and many more.

Software Engineer, Nettium Sdn Bhd

September 2020 — November 2024

- · Create some client requested functions using C# language and stored procedure/SQL.
- Study and follow the current coding style and stored procedure/SQL
- · Code migration.
- · Deploy developed function into Staging and Production environment.
- · Provide support during QAT, cooperate with QA.
- Provide production support during downtime deployment.

Internship, CIMB Malaysia

February 2020 — July 2020

- Learn to use some latest APM tools such as Dynatrace, Splunk, and Nagios.
- · Handle the whole process of monitoring agent implementation.
- Daily basic tasks such as generate utilization report, helping others to solve problems, write minutes of meeting.
- Support other team on Performance Testing.

Education

Bachalor's Degree in Informations Technology (Internet Technology), Tunku Abdul Rahman University College, Setapak, Kuala Lumpur

May 2018 — May 2020

Graduated with a Dean List, CGPA 3.63

Diploma in Information Technology (Internet Technology), Tunku Abdul Rahman University College, Segamat, Johor

May 2016 — May 2018 @ CGPA 3.65

Links

Portfolio Website

OI		
	7	C
	ХШ	12

MySQL	HTML & CSS	HTML & CSS	
SQL	Git		
JavaScript	Java		
Languages			
English	Malay		
Chinese			

Extra-curricular activities

World Skill Malaysia 2019, Kuala Lumpur

March 2019 — September 2019

Finalist in World Skill Malaysia 2019 - IT Track

University Startup Challenge 2020, Kuala Lumpur

May 2020 — September 2020

Pitch idea about new innovative e-commerce idea. Get shortlisted by the organizer.

References

References available upon request